[{"answer": "For once in a while I'm extremely grateful for your British roots.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "... and most of his party think he's crackers (ph)?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "Smart and remarkably -- we had a really good blunt relationship.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "What he really thinks of Vladimir Putin?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Brutally blunt.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "How blunt?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, first, all the problems are probably being intensified by the economic challenges we face.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "What is your take on on where we are?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "LINTON: Well, first of all, I think it's an interesting commentary on the world in which we're living that admitting that the holocaust occurred, qualified (ph) as being a moderate.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "How much do you trust him?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "No, we don't have to believe it.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "And it's just going to happen?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Smart and remarkably -- we had a really good blunt relationship.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What was he like behind closed doors away from, you know, the public utterances?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Brutally blunt.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "How blunt?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Did you talked to him on the phone?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Can you just share with us a little bit about why you think that's so important?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "The day after tomorrow, my wife because she's had more experience.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Well, coming to your family as you're talking women in the workforce, who do you think might make the better president, your wife or your daughter?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Can you put as all out of our misery?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "We worked it out when he was trying to run me out of town.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "What is the ways first, you and Newt Gingrich eventually worked it up between you -- how do you get stuff done in this dysfunctional Washington?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Because consistently, with the single exception of my getting reelected in 1996, the people who agree with us on the gun issue have not been able to protect the people they elect.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Why did they do that?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "No, it is not.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Isn't it about political (ph) courage?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "He does.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Does he do a good Bono impression?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "He does.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "He does?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "It was pretty good.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Now, first of all, what was your reaction when you heard Bono pretending to be you?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "I'm grateful that I have a proud father.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "And most certainly got run to America, second thoughts?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Well, there's people that's been asking me that question for as long as I can remember, literally.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Have you ever thought of, you know, running for high office?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "... this is what I mean.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "It's true, right?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "So, we generally are a card playing family.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "And if so, who wins?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Oh, we play pinochle, spades, hearts, all variant ...", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Which card games?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Thankfully, it's a pretty equal distribution.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Who wins?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "So -- in cards probably.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "You tell me, you all win 33 percent of the time, right?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "I do really want a traditional board games, backgammon, checkers.", "docId": "130925pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "What are you best at?", "qSentId": 501}]